Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Office of the Chancellor Records, 1933-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1933-2011, UWM Archival Collection 46; 220.4 cubic ft. (224 boxes) 2 film reels 718 digital files (539 MB)
  - 1. Klotsche Administration Records, 1933-1980
    - Department of Home Economics, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Department of Housing, Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Department of Intercollegiate Athletics, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Department of Linguistics, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Department of Mathematics, 1958-1972 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Department of Meteorology Proposal, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Department of Music, 1958-1969 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Department of Physical Education, 1959-1965 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Department of Physics, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Department of Planning and Development, 1962-1966 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Department of Political Science, 1959-1969 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Department of Psychology, 1959-1969 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Department of Public Instruction, 1961-1968 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Department of Religious Studies, 1967-1972 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Department of Secondary Education, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Department of Spanish and Portuguese, 1959-1970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Department of Student Counseling, 1960-1970 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Department of Urban Affairs, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 28-29)
    - Disadvantaged Students, Special Projects, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Disruptions and Disturbances, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Division of Commerce, 1958-1966 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Door County Cultural Center, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Dormitories, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Drake University, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Drugs on Campus, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - East Side Community Council, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Ecce Homo Gift, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Economic Education, 1962-1969 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Economic Freeze, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Educational Workers Industrial Union, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Eduplan Project in Venezuela, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 42-43)
    - Eisenscher, Michael [Off-Campus Speaker], 1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Else, Arthur W. [Department of Economics Professor], Mayoral Campaign, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Elvehjem Art Center, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Engineering, 1958-1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Enrollment and Optimum Size of UWM, Report, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Enrollment Statistics 1929-1953 (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - Ethnic Advisory Council, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - European Trip, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Expansion and Acquisition Program, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Extension Division, 1961-1971 (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
    - Faculty and Political Campaigns, 1947-1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Memoranda, 1949-1973 (Box 10, Folder 12-18)
    - Faculty Salary Suit, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Federation of University Assistants, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Financial Aid, 1962-1969 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Flynn, Elizabeth [Off-Campus Speaker], 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Ford Foundation, 1961-1969 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Ford Foundation, Grants, 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Ford Foundation, Urban Proposal, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Foreign Student Affairs, 1959-1969 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Foreign Student Services, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Forging Industry Educational and Research Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Founder's Day Meetings, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Fraternities and Sororities, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Freshman Forum, 1960-1963 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Friends of the UWM Library, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Fromkin Lecture Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Fromkin Memorial Library, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Future of UWM, 1959-1968 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Gifts, 1956-1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Gifts and Grants, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 2-4)
    - Globe Union Foundation Scholarship Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Goethe House, 1961-1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Goodman, Paul [Visiting Professor], 1964 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Commission on Education, Kellett Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
    - Governor's Commission on the United Nations, 1963-1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Governor's Commission on the United Nations, 1973-1980 (Box 11, Folder 11-13)
    - Governor's Commission on the United Nations, Membership Committee, 1975-1982 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Governor's Committee on State Supported Higher Education, 1949-1950 (Box 138, Folder 19)
    - Governor's Conference on Natural Beauty in Wisconsin, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Governor's Task Force on Medical Education, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Faculty Council, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Graduate School, Dean, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Graduate School, Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Graduate School, Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Grants and Contracts, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Grants in Aid for Athletes Project, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Great Plains Regional Instructional Television Library, Correspondence, 1962-1972 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Greater Milwaukee Committee, 1974-1980 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Greene Geological Collection, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Harnischfeger, Walter and Eleanor, Gift of Real Estate, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Hayakawa Speech, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Head Start Teacher Training Program, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Health Examinations, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Health Planning and Policy Task Force, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Hebrew and Semitic Studies, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Higher Education in Wisconsin, Studies and Reports, 1947-1955 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Historical Societies, State and Milwaukee County, 1962-1968 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Holcomb, Edward V., Memorial, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Homosexual Freedom League, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Honor Societies, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1963-1972 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Honors Convocation, 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Hospital Area Planning Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Housing Discrimination, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Identification Card, 1966-1970 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Impact, Incorporated, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Institute of Human Relations, 1964-1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Institute of Human Relations, Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Institute of World Affairs Education, 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - Institute of World Affairs, Governor's Commission on the United Nations, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Institute of World Affairs, Incorporated, 1951-1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Institutional Research, 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Institutional Studies, 1959-1969 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Instructional Communications Center, 1958-1969 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Instructional Media Laboratory, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics, 1963-1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Interim Guidelines for Meeting Academic Obligations During Special Periods and Circumstances, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - International Executive Service Corps, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - International Studies and Programs, 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
    - International Studies and Programs, Office of the Dean, 1962-1965 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - International Task Force, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Interview Policy, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - John Birch Society, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Johnson Foundation, 1961-1969 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Johnson Foundation, 1973-1979 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Jugenheim Pedagogisches Institut, 1953-1960 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Junior League Project, 1961-1966 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Kaleidoscope, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Kearney and Trecker Foundation, 1962-1972 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Kearney and Trecker Foundation, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Kenilworth Property, U.S. Air Force Plant #58, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald, Memorial Fund, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Kenwood Conference Center, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Kenwood Corporation, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Knapp Professorship Committee, 1957-1969 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Knowles, Warren [Wisconsin Governor], 1965-1969 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Labor Relations Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Laboratory of Biological Surface Studies, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Lake Front Development, Proposal Park Freeway, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Lake Side Community Council, 1961-1968 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Latin Community, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Law Enforcement Education, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Law School, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - League of Women Voters, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Lectures Committee, 1967-1971 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Legislative University Advisory Housing Committee, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Library, 1959-1968 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Library, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Library, 1977-1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Library Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Library, Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1961-1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Loans and Scholarships, 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Logo and Seal, 1960-1989 (Box 138, Folder 22)
    - Major University Status, 1958-1971 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Marquette University, 1962-1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Marquette University, School of Medicine, 1964-1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Married Student Housing, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Mass Transit Study, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Medical Assistants, 1957-1962 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Medical Center, 1965-1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Medical Center Steering Committee, John L. Doyne [Milwaukee County Executive], 1965-1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Medical School, 1963-1973 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
    - Medical School, Ad Hoc Committee on Program and Curriculum, 1967-1971 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Memorabilia, 1946-1973 (Box 135-137)
    - Memorabilia, 1956-1986, undated (Box 142)
    - Merger of University of Wisconsin and Wisconsin State University Systems, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
    - Merger of University of Wisconsin and Wisconsin State University Systems
      - Decennial Luncheon, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Legislative Chronology, 1949-1955 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Merger Efforts and Implementation, 1947-1971 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Senate Approval, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Metropolitan Center, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Mid-Winter Leadership Seminar, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Midland Lutheran College, 1958-1981 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Midwest Program on Airborne Television Instruction, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Military Science Department, 1956-1972 (Box 13, Folder 27-29)
    - Miller Theatre, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Milwaukee, City of, 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Milwaukee, City of, Common Council, 1963-1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Milwaukee, City of, Department of City Development, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Milwaukee, City of, Mayor's Council on the Arts, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Milwaukee, City of, Office of the Mayor, 1962-1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Milwaukee Journal, 1960-1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Milwaukee Magazine, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Milwaukee Public Library, 1959-1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Milwaukee Public Museum, 1964-1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Milwaukee Public Schools, 1956-1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Milwaukee School Study, 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 12-14)
    - Milwaukee Sentinel, 1958-1972 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Milwaukee Small Business Opportunities Corporation, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Milwaukee Speaks, Radio Program, 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Milwaukee State Teachers College
      - 1946-1973 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Milwaukee State Teacher's College, American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 1942-1950 (Box 138, Folder 25)
      - Association of American Universities, 1936-1948 (Box 138, Folder 26)
      - Brochures, 1923, 1941 (Box 138, Folder 27)
      - Christmas 1943, Aviation Students Brochure, 1943 (Box 138, Folder 28)
      - History, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Nursery School, 1944-1946 (Box 142)
      - Program, 1940 (Box 138, Folder 29)
      - Progressive Education Association of the Milwaukee Area, 1941 (Box 138, Folder 30)
      - School Songs, undated (Box 138, Folder 31)
      - UWM Liaison Committee, 1949-1956 (Box 138, Folder 32)
    - Milwaukee Symphony Orchestra, 1961-1967 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Milwaukee University School, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Milwaukee Urban League, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Milwaukee Urban Observatory, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Milwaukee Vocational School, 1956-1968 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Milwaukee-Downer College, 1958-1964 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Milwaukee-Downer College Appraisal, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Milwaukee-Downer College Buildings, Landmark Designation, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Milwaukee-Downer College Clippings, 1960-1964 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Milwaukee-Downer College Faculty, 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Milwaukee-Downer College, Historical Marker Dedication and Area Research Center Opening, 1965 (Box 138, Folder 23)
    - Milwaukee-Downer College Inventory, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Milwaukee-Downer Seminary, 1957-1961 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Milwaukee-UWM Coordinating Committee, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Mission Statement, 1968-1973 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Model Cities, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Montgomery Ward Foundation, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges, 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - National Commission on Accrediting, 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
    - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, Visitation Reports, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 34)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - National League of Cities, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - National Science Foundation, 1956-1972 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Native American Program, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Need for Post High School Education in the Lake Shore Area of Wisconsin (Klein Report), 1950 (Box 138, Folder 35)
    - Nelson, Gaylord [U.S. Senator], 1963-1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - New Programs at UWM, 1957-1967 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - News Bureau, 1959-1967 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - News Bureau, 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Non-Resident Students, 1966-1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools
      - Accreditation Review, 1968-1970 (Box 138, Folder 36)
      - Accreditation Review, 1969-1972 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Accreditation Review of Ph.D. Program in Anthropology and Economics, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Accreditation Review of Ph.D. Program in Chemistry, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Central Administration Profile, 1969 (Box 138, Folder 37)
      - Institutional Data Book, 1968 (Box 138, Folder 38)
      - Institutional Profile, 1969 (Box 138, Folder 39)
      - J. Martin Klotsche Involvement, 1969-1980 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Request for Preliminary Accreditation of PhD program in Economics and Anthropology, 1970 (Box 138, Folder 40)
      - UWM Visitation, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Visitation Report, 1969-1970 (Box 138, Folder 41)
    - Occupational Therapy Program, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Office of Development, Director [Charles W. Banta], 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Office of the Graduate School, 1960-1972 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Office of the Graduate School, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Office of the Graduate School, Office of the Dean, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Office of the Purchasing Agent, Inventory, 1962-1972 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Oral History Project, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Organization of University Extension and Outreach Activity, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Organizational Charts, 1962-1973 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Organizing Committee, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Orientation for New Faculty and Administrative Personnel, 1969- (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Overload Payments, 1966-1971 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Parking and Transportation, 1958-1970 (Box 16, Folder 4-6)
    - Parking and Transportation, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Parking and Transportation Committee, 1965-1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Peace Corps, 1962-1966 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Peace Corps Advanced Training Projects, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Peace Corps Contractors' Conference, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Pedestrian Bridge, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Pelton Professorship, 1966-1972 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Personal Items, 1951-1972 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1959-1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Photographs, 1946-1973 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Physical Plant, 1965-1969 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Placement Office, 1963-1970 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Pressed Steel Tank Corporation Strike, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Pro Arte Music Series, 1956-1959 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Professorships, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Program Directions, 1972 (Box 138, Folder 42)
    - Project Destiny and Upward Bound Project, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Property Proposals, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Provost Appointment, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Public Administration Course, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Public Functions Committee, 1963-1969 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Public Higher Education in Metropolitan Milwaukee, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Public Welfare Property, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Racial Count, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Radio and Television Station, 1961-1968 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Rank Promotions, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Reason, Action, Purpose [RAP] for the Seventies, 1970-1971 (Box 139, Folder 1-2)
    - Reason, Action, Purpose [RAP] for the Seventies, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Recommendations for UW Presidency, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Regent Committees, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Regents, 1953-1956 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Regents, 1955-1962 (Box 16, Folder 35-36)
    - Regents, 1964-1969 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Regents, 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Religion and the University, 1955-1968 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Repertory Theatre Project, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Residence Halls, 1962-1972 (Box 17, Folder 4-6)
    - Retirement Ceremonies, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Retirement Correspondence, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Retirement Dinner, J. Martin Klotsche, Speeches, 1979 (Box 141)
    - Retiring Faculty, 1965-1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - ROTC, 1965-1971 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - ROTC Protest, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Rules and Regulations for Students, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Safety Committee, 1963-1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Salaries, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Scholarships, 1965-1968 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - School Mascot and Colors, 1964-1965 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - School of Architecture, 1961-1968 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - School of Architecture
      - Dean Search and Screen Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Fund Raising, 1963-1970 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - School of Business Administration, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - School of Business Administration, Dean, 1963-1968 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - School of Business Administration, Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - School of Education, 1956-1969 (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
    - School of Education, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - School of Education
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Educational Plaza, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Eduplan Project, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - French-Speaking Africa Project, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - International Education and Programs, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Office of Doctoral Studies in Urban Education, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Office of the Dean, 1957-1965 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Office of the Dean, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Urban Education Doctoral Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - School of Fine Arts, 1965-1974 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - School of Fine Arts
      - Office of the Dean, 1957-1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - School of Education Relationship, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - School of Library and Information Science, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - School of Library and Information Science, Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - School of Library and Information Science, Director, Search and Screen Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - School of Nursing, 1960-1972 (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
    - School of Nursing, Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - School of Social Welfare, 1968-1977 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - School of Social Welfare
      - Ad Hoc Committee on Structure and Organization, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Dean, Search and Screen Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Social Work, 1957-1968 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - School Songs, 1960-1967 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Schreiber Luncheon, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Secretary of the Faculty, 1958-1968 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Secretary of the Faculty, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Secretary of the University, 1977-1984 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Segregated Fee Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Selective Service Law Application for Full-time Students, 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Selective Service Policy, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Seventy-Fifth Anniversary, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Shakespeare Theatre, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Shorewood, Village of, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Site Selection Committee, Third UW Campus Proposal, 1963-1966 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Social Development Commission of Greater Milwaukee, 1964-1966 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Spanish Speaking Community, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Spanish Speaking Outreach Institute, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Special Assistant to the Chancellor [William S. Winogrond], 1970 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Speeches
      - 1951-1973 (Box 19, Folder 1-10)
      - Administration, 1963-1968 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Adult Education, 1959-1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Arts, 1954-1964 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Brazil, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Campus Unrest, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Commencements [Non-UWM], 1943-1976 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Commencements and Convocations, 1947-1973 (Box 19, Folder 17-18)
      - Community Life, 1956-1974 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Education, 1958-1973 (Box 19, Folder 20-23)
      - Higher Education [General], 1957-1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Higher Education (General], 1972-1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)